gamewallpapers.com 2019-02-19

# GameWallpapers.com -

This page has been translated by Google Translate. 

##  Privacy Policy - 11/5/2018 

GameWallpapers.com and CGWallpapers.com are products of Flamy Frog Interactive, located at Oude Deventerstraatweg 94 8017BD in Zwolle. We can change this privacy and cookie policy unilaterally. We therefore advise you to regularly check this policy for changes. Flamy Frog Interactive is responsible for the processing of personal data as shown in this privacy statement. 

##  Personal data that we process 

Flamy Frog Interactive processes your personal data by using our services and / or because you provide them yourself. Below you will find an overview of the personal data that we process. 

Visitors:   
\- Internet browser and device type 

Complementary for members:   
\- E-mail address   
\- Password (encrypted)   
\- IP address   
\- Information about your activities on our website 

Additional for artists:   
\- Payment information   
\- Wallpaper download information and revenues 

##  Special and / or sensitive personal data that we process 

Our website and / or service does not intend to collect data about website visitors who are younger than 16 years. Unless they have permission from parents or guardians. However, we can not check if a visitor is older than 16. We encourage parents to be involved in the online activities of their children, in order to prevent data about children being collected without parental consent. If you are convinced that we have collected personal information about a minor without this permission, please contact us at support@gamewallpapers.com and we will delete this information. 

##  For what purpose and on the basis of which we process personal data 

Flamy Frog Interactive processes your personal data for the following purposes:   
\- Allow visitors to create an account   
\- Allow artists to create an account   
\- Sending our newsletter 

##  Automated decision making 

Flamy Frog Interactive does not take decisions based on automated processing on matters that can have (significant) consequences for people. These are decisions that are taken by computer programs or systems, without involving a person (for example, an employee of Flamy Frog Interactive). 

##  How long we keep personal data 

Flamy Frog Interactive does not store your personal data for longer than is strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which your data is collected. On the basis of applicable administrative obligations, we must keep invoices with your (personal) data, so we will keep this data for as long as the applicable term runs. 

##  Sharing personal data with third parties 

Flamy Frog Interactive only provides to third parties and only if this is necessary for the execution of our agreement with you or to comply with a legal obligation. 

##  Cookies, or similar techniques, that we use 

Flamy Frog Interactive uses functional cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored in the browser of your computer, tablet or smartphone when you first visit this website. Flamy Frog Interactive uses cookies with a purely technical functionality. These ensure that the website works properly and that, for example, your preferred settings are remembered. 

Cookies are also placed on this website by third parties. These are for example advertisers and / or social media companies. Below an overview: 

Cookie: Googly Analytics   
Name: _ga / _gat / _gid   
Function: Analytical cookie that measures website visit  
Storage period: 2 years 

##  View, modify or delete data 

You have the right to view, correct or delete your personal data. In addition, you have the right to withdraw your consent to the data processing or to object to the processing of your personal data by Flamy Frog Interactive and you have the right to data portability. This means that you can submit a request to us to send the personal information we have in your computer file to you or another organization mentioned by you. You can send a request for access, correction, deletion, data transfer of your personal data or request for cancellation of your consent or objection to the processing of your personal data to support@gamewallpapers.com. To ensure that the request for access has been made by you, we ask you to send a copy of your ID with the request. Make your passport photo, MRZ (machine readable zone, the strip with numbers at the bottom of the passport), passport number and citizen service number (BSN) black in this copy. This is to protect your privacy. We respond as quickly as possible, but within four weeks, at your request. 

##  How we protect personal data 

Flamy Frog Interactive takes the protection of your data seriously and takes appropriate measures to prevent misuse, loss, unauthorized access, unwanted disclosure and unauthorized modification. If you have the impression that your data is not secure or there are indications of misuse, please contact our customer service or support@gamewallpapers.com.
